{
    "questions": [
        {
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "When is our anniversary?",
            "correctAnswer": "Nov 4",
            "possibleAnswers": [
                "Oct 29",
                "Nov 2",
                "Nov 4",
                "Nov 8"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "What is our number?",
            "correctAnswer": "4",
            "possibleAnswers": [
                "3",
                "4",
                "12",
                "24"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "When is my birthday?",
            "correctAnswer": "April 12",
            "possibleAnswers": [
                "April 1",
                "April 12",
                "April 14",
                "April 24"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "When am I coming to see you next?",
            "correctAnswer": "March 11",
            "possibleAnswers": [
                "March 8",
                "March 11",
                "March 15",
                "March 16"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "What is my favorite color to wear?",
            "correctAnswer": "Brown",
            "possibleAnswers": [
                "Black",
                "Gray",
                "Brown",
                "White"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "What are my brothers' names?",
            "correctAnswer": "Braylon and Jaden",
            "possibleAnswers": [
                "Braden and Jadon",
                "Brayden and Jaiden",
                "Braylen and Jayden",
                "Braylon and Jaden"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "What is my favorite food?",
            "correctAnswer": "Pizza",
            "possibleAnswers": [
                "Pizza",
                "Burritos",
                "Soup",
                "French toast"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "What is my favorite bird?",
            "correctAnswer": "Black-capped chickadee",
            "possibleAnswers": [
                "Black-billed magpie",
                "Anna's hummingbird",
                "Black-capped chickadee",
                "Domestic pigeon"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "Which one scares me the most?",
            "correctAnswer": "Deep ocean",
            "possibleAnswers": [
                "Heights",
                "Ants",
                "Circus clowns",
                "Deep ocean"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "If I were a Minecraft block, what would I be?",
            "correctAnswer": "Red sand",
            "possibleAnswers": [
                "Red sand",
                "Red sandstone",
                "Redstone ore",
                "Redstone block"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "What is your warrior name?",
            "correctAnswer": "Honeyshade",
            "possibleAnswers": [
                "Maplecloud",
                "Honeyshade",
                "Mapleshade",
                "Honeycloud"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "What is my warrior name?",
            "correctAnswer": "Birchsong",
            "possibleAnswers": [
                "Birchsong",
                "Pebblestep",
                "Birchstep",
                "Pebblesong"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "Who was I on Halloween?",
            "correctAnswer": "Daphne",
            "possibleAnswers": [
                "Daphne",
                "Velma",
                "Gideon",
                "Harrow"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "Where did I NOT visit on my road trip last summer?",
            "correctAnswer": "Detroit",
            "possibleAnswers": [
                "Cincinnati",
                "Chicago",
                "Detroit",
                "Helena"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "What is my favorite movie?",
            "correctAnswer": "Creep",
            "possibleAnswers": [
                "Creep",
                "Creep 2",
                "Searching",
                "But I'm a Cheerleader"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "What is Friend Sr?",
            "correctAnswer": "A cheetah",
            "possibleAnswers": [
                "A giraffe",
                "A cheetah",
                "A leopard",
                "A manatee"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "What do I miss the most about you?",
            "correctAnswer": "Your hugs",
            "possibleAnswers": [
                "Your ****",
                "Your kisses",
                "Your hugs",
                "Your smell"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "What is my favorite flower?",
            "correctAnswer": "Dandelion",
            "possibleAnswers": [
                "Daffodil",
                "Tulip",
                "Dandelion",
                "Daisy"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "What're our names in It Takes Two?",
            "correctAnswer": "May and Cody",
            "possibleAnswers": [
                "Maya and Cliff",
                "May and Cliff",
                "Maya and Cody",
                "May and Cody"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "What am I a little bit after taking a shower?",
            "correctAnswer": "A damp rat",
            "possibleAnswers": [
                "A wet rat",
                "A damp rat",
                "A moist mouse",
                "A drenched rodent"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "What is your name on Snapchat for me?",
            "correctAnswer": "lil soup ü•£",
            "possibleAnswers": [
                "‚ù§Ô∏è Ethan ‚ù§Ô∏è",
                "‚ù§Ô∏è lil soup ‚ù§Ô∏è",
                "Ethan ü•£",
                "lil soup ü•£"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "What age was I kicked out?",
            "correctAnswer": "16",
            "possibleAnswers": [
                "15",
                "16",
                "17",
                "18"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "Where is my power button?",
            "correctAnswer": "Back of neck",
            "possibleAnswers": [
                "Forehead",
                "Back of neck",
                "Middle of back",
                "Top of head"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "What state am I going to live in after graduation?",
            "correctAnswer": "GA",
            "possibleAnswers": [
                "WA",
                "OR",
                "GA",
                "CA"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "How bad is my memory?",
            "correctAnswer": "Absolutely awful",
            "possibleAnswers": [
                "Not at all bad",
                "Sometimes forgetful",
                "Bad enough you'd repeat a question",
                "Absolutely awful"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "How bad is my memory?",
            "correctAnswer": "Bad enough you'd repeat a question",
            "possibleAnswers": [
                "Not at all bad",
                "Sometimes forgetful",
                "Bad enough you'd repeat a question",
                "Absolutely awful"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "Which lyric is from the first song of yours I hyperfixated on?",
            "correctAnswer": "This ain't monogamy / Y'all gettin' fucked",
            "possibleAnswers": [
                "This ain't Monopoly / Watchin' for love / This ain't monogamy / Y'all gettin' fucked",
                "My left stroke just went viral / Right stroke put lil' baby in a spiral",
                "Goddamn I got bitches (okay!) / damn I got bitches (okay!)",
                "This is how I feel / If somebody kill my son that mean somebody's gettin' killed"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "Which sport did I NOT play in middle school?",
            "correctAnswer": "Bowling",
            "possibleAnswers": [
                "Soccer",
                "Basketball",
                "Bowling",
                "Cheerleading"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "What is my #1 love language?",
            "correctAnswer": "Acts of service",
            "possibleAnswers": [
                "Physical touch",
                "Words of affirmation",
                "Quality time",
                "Acts of service"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "Who do I need to see?",
            "correctAnswer": "All of the above",
            "possibleAnswers": [
                "A therapist",
                "A dentist",
                "A doctor",
                "All of the above"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "How many sittings does it take for me to finish a movie with you?",
            "correctAnswer": "Either 1 or 4",
            "possibleAnswers": [
                "Only 1",
                "Anywhere from 1 to 4",
                "Either 1 or 4",
                "Always 4 or more"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "What is my current #1 best day?",
            "correctAnswer": "Day we went to Seattle",
            "possibleAnswers": [
                "Day we started dating",
                "Day you showed me around Marysville",
                "Day we went to Seattle",
                "Day I left"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "What is our current longest call?",
            "correctAnswer": "~48 hours",
            "possibleAnswers": [
                "~24 hours",
                "~36 hours",
                "~48 hours",
                "~60 hours"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "How much do I love you?",
            "correctAnswer": "Too much",
            "possibleAnswers": [
                "A little bit",
                "Somewhat",
                "A lot",
                "Too much"
            ]
        }
    ]
}